JIMMY LAROCHE

WEB DEVELOPER

INFO

ADDRESS

237 Aspen Stone Pl Sw T3H 0H5 Calgary, Alberta

PHONE

587.707.3101

WEB

www.jimmylaroche.com www.linkedin.com/in/jimmylaroche

EMAIL

contact@jimmylaroche.com

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP

WordPress. Webflow

Adobe Suite

Google Sheets, Trends, Analytics

Search Engine Optimization

Time Management

Team Player

Adaptable

LANGUAGES

English

French

PROFILE

Self-motivated, teachable and highly reliable individual looking to be challenged. Recent graduate from a comprehensive 2 year course in New Media Production & Design with a strong focus on web development for a career in the new media industry.

WORK HISTORY

Web Development Intern, JYZ Design

Calgary, AB

January 2020 - March 2020

- Provided assistance building and updating WordPress websites
- Created custom code for specific functionalities
- Created a "link soup" for JYZ Design's website to help with their SEO

Web Developer, Access52

Calgary, AB

August 2019 - Present

- · Plan all site designs, functionality and navigation
- Build wireframes and prototypes and transform them into responsive websites
- Develop custom admin panels to allow clients to add, delete and edit data

Grocery Clerk, Blushlane

Calgary, AB

December 2016 - August 2019

- Demonstrated attention to detail when handling the store's database
- Regularly ordered products from different vendors in a timely fashion to ensure the store had adequate supplies
- Delivered excellent customer service by educating customers on different organic products

EDUCATION

Diploma in New Media Production & Design

SAIT - Calgary, AB

September 2018 - April 2020

AEC (College Education Attestation)

Cégep Limoilou- Quebec, QC

in Multimedia

May 2013 - September 2014